JESSE BETT

Software Developer | +254798790147

PROFILE

O DETAILS O

0798790147

jessekip21@gmail.com

I'm a software developer whose primary goal is to apply technical expertise all throughout the full software life cycle to ensure the production and delivery of world-class products and services that meet client specifications. Along with a competent software development team, and with strong personal knowledge, skills, and experience in software engineering. I'm passionate about solving problems, understanding how things work and how I could improve them.

O SKILLS O

JavaScript

TypeScript

Angular

React

ExpressJs

JWT Auth

Python

GraphQL

Mongo

SQL

NestJs

Version control

O HOBBIES O

Football

Chess

Hiking

O LINKS O

https://jessebett.vercel.app https://github.com/Jesse-Bett

EDUCATION

Kabarak University, Nakuru, Kenya

BSc. Information Technology

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Fasi Health - Full Stack Developer

August 2023 - Current

Duties/Responsibilities.

- Coding and maintaining Fasi Reporsitories.
- Configuring annd managing pipelines.
- Configuring cognito user pools.
- Collaborate with other team members to ship features.
- Testing and debugging software

Fameve - Software Developer

November 2022 - August 2023

Duties/Responsibilities.

- Code and maintain the front-end.
- Design and implement user-friendly interfaces.
- Optimize the user experience.
- Collaborate with other team members to ship features.
- Testing and debugging software

JamboPay

May 2022 - November 2022

Duties/Responsibilities.

- Performing web integrations between customer website and JamboPay checkout.
- Developing and maintaining our email and SMS systems.
- Developing e-commerce web apps to assist in testing integration plugins and writing API documentation.
- Monitoring Jambopay systems to detect and resolve downtime.
- Supporting internal staff in network, hardware, and software issues.

REFEREES

Patrick Mwangi

Senior backend engineer - Jambopay

+254723092547

Laban Kiplagat

Senior frontend engineer - Fameve

+254703248870